Rose Gerlach Slide Collection
Yale University Arts Library
- Halkin, Theodore, b. 1924 (1 slide) (Box 4)
  - Parke Bernet gallery, 1964 (Box 4)
- Hall, David, b. 1937 (4 slides) (Box 4)
  - Feigen gallery, 1966 (Box 4)
- Hall, Marks (1 slide) (Box 4)
  - Royal Marks gallery, 1970 (Box 4)
- Han, H.N., b. 1939 (2 slides) (Box 4)
  - O.K. Harris gallery, 1971 (Box 4)
- Hanafusa (3 slides) (Box 4)
  - Stable gallery, 1969 (Box 4)
- Hanson, Duane, 1925-1996 (5 slides) (Box 4)
  - O.K. Harris gallery, 1972 (Box 4)
- Harris, Paul, b. 1925 (3 slides) (Box 4)
  - Poindexter gallery, 1967 (Box 4)
- Harrison, Tony, b. 1931 (7 slides) (Box 4)
  - Schaefer gallery, 1968, 1972 (Box 4)
- Hartell, John Anthony, b. 1902 (7 slides) (Box 4)
  - Kraushaer gallery, 1966 (Box 4)
- Hartigan, Grace, b. 1922 (9 slides) (Box 4)
  - Jackson gallery, 1967, 1970 (Box 4)
- Hartl, Leon (12 slides) (Box 4)
  - Zabriskie gallery, 1968 (Box 4)
- Hartley, Marsden, 1877-1943 (1 slide) [Slide box 20] (Box 4)
  - Forum gallery, 1968 (Box 4)
- Hartman, Robert (4 slides) (Box 4)
  - Schaefer gallery, 1969 (Box 4)
- Hartung, Hans, 1904-1989 (8 slides) (Box 4)
  - Emmerich gallery, 1966 (Box 4)
  - Lefebre gallery, 1971 (Box 4)
- Hatcher, B. (2 slides) (Box 4)
  - Emmerich gallery, 1973 (Box 4)
- Haupt, Theodore Gilbert, b. 1902 (17 slides) (Box 4)
  - Emmerich gallery, 1966 (Box 4)
  - East Hampton gallery, 1968 (Box 4)
- Harvey, Robert, b. 1924 (3 slides) (Box 4)
  - Krasner gallery, 1969 (Box 4)
- Hatchett, Duayne, b. 1925 (4 slides) (Box 4)
  - Royal Marks gallery, 1969 (Box 4)
- Hausman (3 slides) (Box 4)
  - Bodley gallery, 1969 (Box 4)
- Hay, Alex, b. 1930 (18 slides) (Box 4)
  - Kornblee gallery, 1967, 1968, 1969 (Box 4)
- Heade, Martin Johnson, 1819-1904 (1 slide) (Box 4)
  - Whitney Slide "Hummingbirds and Orchids," 1875 (Box 4)
- Healey, John (4 slides) (Box 4)
  - Waddell gallery, 1969 (Box 4)
- Hedge, Gene (5 slides) (Box 4)
  - Poindexter gallery, 1968 (Box 4)
- Heerich, Erwin, b. 1922 (6 slides) (Box 4)
  - Dwan gallery, 1968 (Box 4)
- Heilmann, Mary, b. 1940 (2 slides) (Box 4)
  - Paley and Lowe gallery, 1972 (Box 4)
- Held, Al, b. 1928 (17 slides) (Box 4)
  - Emmerich gallery, 1967, 1968, 1970, 1972, 1973 (Box 4)
- Helioff, Anne, 1910-2001 (7 slides) (Box 4)
  - Capricorn gallery, 1969 (Box 4)
- Hendler, Raymond, 1923-1998 (7 slides) (Box 4)
  - Rose Fried gallery, 1967 (Box 4)
- Hendricks (6 slides) (Box 4)
  - Bianchini gallery, 1966 (Box 4)
- Hendricks (8 slides) (Box 4)
  - Ruth White gallery, 1968 (Box 4)
- Hennesy (5 slides) (Box 4)
  - de Nagy gallery, 1970 (Box 4)
- Henry, Dale, b. 1931 (2 slides) (Box 4)
  - Fischbach gallery, 1971 (Box 4)
- Herbin, Auguste, 1882-1960 (2 slides) (Box 4)
  - Denise René gallery, 1973 (Box 4)
- Heron, Patrick, 1920-1999 (4 slides) (Box 4)
  - Schaefer gallery, 1965 (Box 4)
- Hershon (8 slides) (Box 4)
  - Bodley gallery, 1966 (Box 4)
- Hess, Minda (1 slide) (Box 4)
  - Amel gallery, 1965 (Box 4)
- Hesse, Eva, 1936-1970 (9 slides) (Box 4)
  - Fischbach gallery, 1966, 1968, 1970 (Box 4)
- Hinman, Charles B., b. 1932 (24 slides) (Box 4)
  - Feigen gallery, 1964, 1965, 1966 (Box 4)
  - Denise René gallery, 1972, 1973 (Box 4)
- Hiquily (1 slide) (Box 4)
  - Contemporaries gallery, 1964 (Box 4)
- Hirsch, Gilah Yelin, b. 1944 (2 slides) [Slide box 21] (Box 4)
  - de Nagy gallery, 1972 (Box 4)
- Hirsch, Joseph, 1910-1981 (3 slides) (Box 4)
  - Forum gallery, 1969 (Box 4)
- Hitchcock, Ray, b. 1937 (1 slide) (Box 4)
  - Hutchinson gallery, 1972 (Box 4)
- Hobbs, Fred (2 slides) (Box 4)
  - 20th Century West gallery, 1966 (Box 4)
- Hockney, David, b. 1937 (6 slides) (Box 4)
  - Emmerich gallery, 1969 (Box 4)
- Hodgkins, Rosalind (1 slide) (Box 4)
  - Benedek gallery, 1973 (Box 4)
- Hoff, Margo, b. 1912 (16 slides) (Box 4)
  - Banfer gallery, 1966, 1968 (Box 4)
- Hoffman, Martin, b. 1935 (3 slides) (Box 4)
  - O.K. Harris gallery, 1973 (Box 4)
- Hofman, George (4 slides) (Box 4)
  - French gallery, 1971 (Box 4)
- Hofmann, Hans, 1880-1966 (40 slides) (Box 4)
  - Parke Bernet gallery, 1964 (Box 4)
  - Emmerich gallery, 1967, 1968, 1969, 1970, 1971, 1972, 1973, 1974 (Box 4)
- Hokanson, Hans, b. 1925 (5 slides) (Box 4)
  - Fischbach gallery, 1965 (Box 4)
  - Borgenicht gallery, 1968 (Box 4)
- Holbrook (1 slide) (Box 4)
  - M. Jackson gallery, 1967 (Box 4)
- Holland, Tom, b. 1936 (5 slides) (Box 4)
  - Elkon gallery, 1970, 1971 (Box 4)
  - Rubin gallery, 1972 (Box 4)
- Hollister, Valerie, b. 1939 (2 slides) (Box 4)
  - West Broadway gallery, 1973 (Box 4)
- Hollweg, Alexander (6 slides) (Box 4)
  - Kornblee gallery, 1983, 1984 (Box 4)
- Holty, Carl Robert, 1900-1973 (7 slides) (Box 4)
  - Graham gallery, 1967 (Box 4)
  - Poindexter gallery, 1972 (Box 4)
- Honegger (5 slides) (Box 4)
  - Jackson gallery, 1964 (Box 4)
- Honneger, Gottfried, b. 1917 (2 slides) (Box 4)
  - Gimpel gallery, 1970 (Box 4)
- Hoover, Nan, b. 1931 (2 slides) (Box 4)
  - Spectrum gallery, 1969 (Box 4)
- Hopkins, Budd, b. 1931 (20 slides) (Box 4)
  - Poindexter gallery, 1967, 1969, 1971 (Box 4)
- Hornak, Ian, born 1944 (2 slides) (Box 4)
  - de Nagy gallery, 1971 (Box 4)
- Horowitz, I. (aka Applebroog, Ida, b. 1929) (2 slides) (Box 4)
  - Hutchinson gallery, 1973 (Box 4)
- Houser, Jim, b. 1928 (13 slides) (Box 4)
  - Grand Central Moderns, 1967 (Box 4)
- Howard, Charles Houghton, 1899-1978 (2 slides) (Box 4)
  - Wise gallery, 1965 (Box 4)
- Howard, Robert Boardman, 1896-1983 (3 slides) (Box 4)
  - Royal Marks gallery, 1969 (Box 4)
- Howe, Nelson (7 slides) (Box 4)
  - East Hampton gallery, 1968 (Box 4)
- Hoyland, John, b. 1934 (10 slides) (Box 4)
  - Elkon gallery, 1967, 1969 (Box 4)
  - Emmerich gallery, 1970, 1972 (Box 4)
- Hudson, Gary (1 slide) (Box 4)
  - Reese Palley gallery, 1971 (Box 4)
- Hudson, Robert, b. 1938 (7 slides) (Box 4)
  - Frumkin gallery, 1965, 1969, 1971 (Box 4)
- Huggins (3 slides) (Box 4)
  - Schaefer gallery, 1970 (Box 4)
- Hughto, Darryl, b. 1943 (5 slides) (Box 4)
  - de Nagy gallery, 1971, 1974 (Box 4)
- Hulse (14 slides) (Box 4)
  - 14 slides (Box 4)
- Hultberg, John, 1922-2005 (7 slides) [Slide box 22] (Box 4)
  - Jackson gallery, 1969, 1972 (Box 4)
- Humphrey, Ralph, 1932-1990 (12 slides) (Box 4)
  - Bykert gallery, 1969, 1970 (Box 4)
  - Emmerich gallery, 1971 (Box 4)
- Hundertwasser, Friedensreich, 1928-2000 (12 slides) (Box 4)
  - Austrian Pavillion, 1964 (Box 4)
- Huntington, Jim, b. 1941 (3 slides) (Box 4)
  - Hutchinson gallery, 1971, 1973 (Box 4)
- Huot, Robert, b. 1935 (2 slides) (Box 4)
  - Radich gallery, 1964 (Box 4)
- Hussey, Howard, b. 1938 (2 slides) (Box 4)
  - 20th century West gallery, 1966 (Box 4)
- Huxley, Paul, b. 1938 (6 slides) (Box 4)
  - Kornblee gallery, 1970 (Box 4)
- Hybrid (4 slides) (Box 4)
  - Kornblee gallery, 1966 (Box 4)
- Inconiglios, Vincent (1 slide) (Box 4)
  - West Broadway gallery, 1973 (Box 4)
- Indiana, Robert, b. 1928 (13 slides) (Box 4)
  - Stable gallery, 1964, 1966 (Box 4)
- Ingermann (4 slides) (Box 4)
  - Hammer gallery, 1968 (Box 4)
- Inokuma, Gen'ichiro, b. 1902 (7 slides) (Box 4)
  - Willard gallery, 1964, 1968 (Box 4)
- Insley, Will, b. 1929 (8 slides) (Box 4)
  - Stable gallery, 1965 (Box 4)
- Inukai, Kyohei, 1913-1985 (2 slides) (Box 4)
  - Spectrum gallery, 1968 (Box 4)
- Iranyi, Helen (4 slides) (Box 4)
  - Spectrum gallery, 1968, 1969 (Box 4)
- Irwin, Robert, b. 1928 (4 slides) (Box 4)
  - Pace gallery, 1971 (Box 4)
- Isham, Sheila Eaton, b. 1927 (1 slide) (Box 4)
  - Fischbach gallery, 1973 (Box 4)
- Isobe (3 slides) (Box 4)
  - Staempfli gallery, 1965 (Box 4)
- Israel, Margaret, 1929-1987 (3 slides) (Box 4)
  - Cordier-Ekstrom gallery, 1971 (Box 4)
- Israel, Marvin, 1924-1985 (8 slides) (Box 4)
  - Cordier-Ekstrom gallery, 1966, 1969 (Box 4)
- Israel, Murray (4 slides) (Box 4)
  - Fried gallery, 1966 (Box 4)
- Ives, Norman Seaton, 1923-1978 (2 slides) (Box 4)
  - Wise gallery, 1964 (Box 4)
- Iwasab (4 slides) (Box 4)
  - Banfer gallery, 1969 (Box 4)
- Iwasaki, Taku (4 slides) (Box 4)
  - Grippi-Waddell gallery, 1965 (Box 4)
- Jackson, Richard, b. 1939 (1 slide) (Box 4)
  - Bykert gallery, 1973 (Box 4)
- Jacobs, Harold, b. 1932 (2 slides) (Box 4)
  - Amel gallery, 1964 (Box 4)
- Jacoby, Ruth (8 slides) (Box 4)
  - Bodley gallery, 1968 (Box 4)
- Jacquet, Alain, b. 1939 (7 slides) (Box 4)
  - Waddell gallery, 1968, 1969 (Box 4)
- Jacquette, Yvonne Helene, b. 1934 (8 slides) (Box 4)
  - Fischbach gallery, 1971, 1982, 1983 (Box 4)
- James, Lawrence (1slide) (Box 4)
  - Weber gallery, 1972 (Box 4)
- Janis, Maria (2 slides) (Box 4)
  - Bodley gallery, 1971 (Box 4)
- Jansons, Andrew, b. 1945 (3 slides) (Box 4)
  - Myers gallery, 1971 (Box 4)
- Japanese Art Festival, 1966 (16 slides) (Box 4)
  - Various Artists (Box 4)
- Jarvaise, James (4 slides) (Box 4)
  - Landau-Alan gallery, 1967 (Box 4)
- Jeffrey, Carlin (4 slides) (Box 4)
  - O.K. Harris gallery, 1971 (Box 4)
- Jenkins, Paul, b. 1923 (36 slides) (Box 4)
  - Amel gallery, 1965 (Box 4)
  - Jackson gallery, 1966, 1967, 1968, 1969, 1970, 1971 (Box 4)
- Jensen, Alfred, 1903-1981 (22 slides) [Slide box 23] (Box 4)
  - Martha Jackson gallery, 1964 (Box 4)
  - Graham gallery, 1965 (Box 4)
  - Royal Marks gallery, 1966 (Box 4)
  - Cordier-Ekstrom gallery, 1968, 1970 (Box 4)
- Jensen, Bill, b. 1945 (1 slide) (Box 4)
  - Fischbach gallery, 1973 (Box 4)
- Jensen, Leo (9 slides) (Box 4)
  - Amel gallery, 1965 (Box 4)
  - Fischbach gallery, 1973 (Box 4)
- Jernigan (5 slides) (Box 4)
  - Whitehouse gallery, 1966 (Box 4)
- Jimenez, Luis (5 slides) (Box 4)
  - Graham gallery, 1969, 1970 (Box 4)
  - O.K. Harris gallery, 1972 (Box 4)
- Johansen (1 slide) (Box 4)
  - Tibor de Nagy gallery, 1966 (Box 4)
- Johns, Jasper, b. 1930 (6 slides) (Box 4)
  - Castelli gallery, 1968, 1969 (Box 4)
- Johnson, Ben (10 slides) (Box 4)
  - Selected Artists gallery, 1966 (Box 4)
- Johnson, Buffie, 1912-2006 (3 slides) (Box 4)
  - Hutchinson gallery, 1973 (Box 4)
- Johnson, Lester F., b. 1919 (6 slides) (Box 4)
  - Martha Jackson gallery, 1969, 1971 (Box 4)
- Johnson, Michael, b. 1938 (2 slides) (Box 4)
  - Hutchinson gallery, 1973 (Box 4)
- Johnson, Ray, 1927-1994 (15 slides) (Box 4)
  - Willard gallery, 1965, 1966 (Box 4)
  - Feigen gallery, 1968 (Box 4)
- Jolis, Rosetta, active 1959-1960 (2slides) (Box 4)
  - Bodley gallery, 1969 (Box 4)
- Jones, Allen, b. 1937 (4 slides) (Box 4)
  - AFA gallery, 1966 (Box 4)
  - Feigen gallery, 1970 (Box 4)
- Jones, Howard (4 slides) (Box 4)
  - Wise gallery, 1968 (Box 4)
- Jordan, Robert, b. 1925 (7 slides) (Box 4)
  - Banfer gallery, 1969 (Box 4)
- Jordon (1 slide) (Box 4)
  - Bodley gallery, 1971 (Box 4)
- Jorn, Asger, 1914-1973 (10 slides) (Box 4)
  - Lefebre gallery, 1967, 1970 (Box 4)
- Judd, Donald, 1928-1994 (8 slides) (Box 4)
  - Castelli gallery, 1969, 1970, 1973 (Box 4)
- Kacere, John C., 1920-1999 (7 slides) (Box 4)
  - O.K. Harris gallery, 1971, 1973 (Box 4)
- Kahn, Wolf, b. 1927 (16 slides) (Box 4)
  - Borgenicht gallery, 1967, 1969 (Box 4)
- Kaisch, Morton (1 slide) (Box 4)
  - Staempfli gallery, 1971 (Box 4)
- Kaish, Luise, b. 1925 (4 slides) (Box 4)
  - Staempfli gallery, 1968 (Box 4)
- Kalina, Richard, b. 1946 (2 slides) (Box 4)
  - O.K. Harris gallery, 1970 (Box 4)
- Kallem, Henry (2 slides) (Box 4)
  - East Hampton gallery, 1969 (Box 4)
- Kaltenbach, Steven J., b. 1940 (2 slides) (Box 4)
  - Reese Palley gallery, 1972 (Box 4)
- Kamys, Walter (3 slides) (Box 4)
  - East Hampton gallery, 1970 (Box 4)
- Kane, Bob (5 slides) (Box 4)
  - Schaeffer gallery, 1968, 1972 (Box 4)
- Kangas, Gene (1 slide) (Box 4)
  - Royal Marks gallery, 1970 (Box 4)
- Kano (2 slides) (Box 4)
  - Staempfli gallery, 1965 (Box 4)
- Kanowitz (16 slides) (Box 4)
  - Waddell gallery, 1969, 1971 (Box 4)
- Kantor, Morris, 1896-1974 (6 slides) (Box 4)
  - Schaeffer gallery, 1971 (Box 4)
- Kantor, Tadeusz, 1915-1990 (2 slides) (Box 4)
  - D'Arcy gallery, 1965 (Box 4)
- Kaplan, Jacques (7 slides) [Slide box 24] (Box 4)
  - Waddell gallery, 1967 (Box 4)
- Karoly (11 slides) (Box 4)
  - Castellane gallery, 1965 (Box 4)
- Kasuba, Aleksandra, b. 1923 (3 slides) (Box 4)
  - Grippi-Waddell gallery, 1965 (Box 4)
- Kasumoto (1 slide) (Box 4)
  - Radich gallery, 1966 (Box 4)
- Katan, Roger (1 slide) (Box 4)
  - Wise gallery, 1967 (Box 4)
- Katz, Alex, b. 1927 (18 slides) (Box 4)
  - Fischbach gallery, 1967, 1968, 1969, 1970, 1971 (Box 4)
- Katz, Paul (1 slide) (Box 4)
  - Sachs gallery, 1971 (Box 4)
- Kauffman, Craig, b. 1932 (12 slides) (Box 4)
  - Pace gallery, 1967, 1969, 1970, 1973 (Box 4)
- Kaufman, Donald, b. 1935 (4 slides) (Box 4)
  - Feigen gallery, 1966, 1971 (Box 4)
- Kaufman, Jane A., b. 1938 (3 slides0 (Box 4)
  - Sachs gallery, 1968 (Box 4)
- Kaupelis, Robert John, b. 1928 (17 slides) (Box 4)
  - Castagna gallery, 1966 (Box 4)
  - Schaefer gallery, 1969 (Box 4)
- Kawai (6 slides) (Box 4)
  - Schaefer gallery, 1968 (Box 4)
- Kawashima, Takeshi, b. 1930 (10 slides) (Box 4)
  - Waddell gallery, 1967 (Box 4)
- Kearl, Stanley B., 1914-1998 (5 slides) (Box 4)
  - Grand Central Moderns, 1968 (Box 4)
- Kearney, Nancy Jean, b. 1941 (5 slides) (Box 4)
  - ACA gallery, 1964 (Box 4)
- Keck, Hardu (1 slide) (Box 4)
  - Benedek gallery, 1973 (Box 4)
- Kelemen, Steve (2 slides) (Box 4)
  - Spectrum gallery, 1972 (Box 4)
- Keller, Harold (3 slides) (Box 4)
  - Spectrum gallery, 1967 (Box 4)
- Kelly, James (6 slides) (Box 4)
  - East Hampton gallery, 1965 (Box 4)
  - AFA, 1966 (Box 4)
- Kelsey-Castelane (Exhibition?) (4 slides) (Box 4)
  - 1964 (Box 4)
- Kendall (1 slide) (Box 4)
  - Greenross gallery, 1964 (Box 4)
- Kenney, Leo, 1925-2001 (1 slide) (Box 4)
  - Willard gallery, 1968 (Box 4)
- Kent, Rockwell, 1882-1971 (2 slides) (Box 4)
  - Larcada gallery, 1969 (Box 4)
- Kepler (1slide) (Box 4)
  - Gibson gallery, 1973 (Box 4)
- Kerns, Ed, b. 1945 (2 slides) (Box 4)
  - Sachs gallery, 1972 (Box 4)
- Kerr, Pamela (3 slides) (Box 4)
  - Schaefer gallery, 1967 (Box 4)
- Kienholz, Edward, 1927-1994 (13 slides) (Box 4)
  - Dwan gallery, 1965, 1967 (Box 4)
- Kiesler, Frederick John, 1890-1965 (10 slides) (Box 4)
  - Jackson gallery, 1966, 1967 (Box 4)
  - Wise gallery, 1969 (Box 4)
- Kilby, Ruth (3 slides) (Box 4)
  - Bodley gallery, 1966 (Box 4)
- Kimball, Jeffe (4 slides) (Box 4)
  - Rehn gallery, 1968 (Box 4)
- King, Anthony (1 slide) (Box 4)
  - O.K. Harris gallery, 1972 (Box 4)
- King, Philip (3 slides) (Box 4)
  - Feigen gallery, 1966 (Box 4)
- King, William, b. 1925 (22 slides) (Box 4)
  - Dintenfass gallery, 1964, 1965, 1966, 1967, 1968, 1969, 1971 (Box 4)
- Kings, John (26 slides) [Slide box 25] (Box 5)
  - Bodley gallery, 1966 (Box 5)
- Kinigstein, Jonah, b. 1923 (6 slides) (Box 5)
  - Nordness gallery, 1964 (Box 5)
- Kinsella (15 slides) (Box 5)
  - Capricorn gallery, 1966 (Box 5)
- Kipnis, Robert (8 slides) (Box 5)
  - Contemporaries gallery, 1967 (Box 5)
- Kirschen-Cole, Stephanie, b. 1945 (2 slides) (Box 5)
  - de Nagy gallery, 1980, 1983 (Box 5)
- Kirschenbaum, Bernard Edwin, b. 1924 (3 slides) (Box 5)
  - Paula Cooper gallery, 1971, 1972 (Box 5)
- Kirschenbaum, Jules, b. 1930 (6 slides) (Box 5)
  - Forum gallery, 1969, 1972 (Box 5)
- Kitchel, Nancy, b. 1941 (1 slide) (Box 5)
  - AIR gallery, 1973 (Box 5)
- Kiyooka, Roy Kenzie, 1926-1994 (9 slides) (Box 5)
  - Grippi-Waddell gallery, 1966 (Box 5)
- Klavun, Betty (3 slides) (Box 5)
  - Schaeffer gallery, 1971, 1972 (Box 5)
- Kleeman, Ron, b. 1937 (2 slides) (Box 5)
  - French gallery, 1971 (Box 5)
- Klein, Morris (2 slides) (Box 5)
  - Bodley gallery, 1969 (Box 5)
- Klem, Grace (1 slide) (Box 5)
  - Bodley gallery, 1972 (Box 5)
- Kline, Harriet (4 slides) (Box 5)
  - Selected Artists, 1968 (Box 5)
- Kliros, Theodore (1 slide) (Box 5)
  - Schaefer gallery, 1965 (Box 5)
- Knaths, Karl, 1891-1971 (4 slides) (Box 5)
  - Rosenberg gallery, 1972 (Box 5)
- Kobashi (6 slides) (Box 5)
  - Alan Stone gallery, 1965 (Box 5)
- Koenig, Fritz, b. 1924 (2 slides) (Box 5)
  - Staempfli gallery, 1967 (Box 5)
- Kolin, Sasche (13 slides) (Box 5)
  - East Hampton gallery, 1965 (Box 5)
- Komodore, Bill (14 slides) (Box 5)
  - Wise gallery, 1964, 1966 (Box 5)
- Konna (1 slide) (Box 5)
  - Staempfli gallery, 1965 (Box 5)
- Konzal, Joseph, 1905-1995 (2 slides) (Box 5)
  - Schaefer gallery, 1971 (Box 5)
- Kortlander (8 slides) (Box 5)
  - Sachs gallery, 1967, 1968 (Box 5)
- Kos, Paul Joseph, b. 1942 (2 slides) (Box 5)
  - Reese-Palley gallery, 1972 (Box 5)
  - Castelli gallery, 1973 (Box 5)
- Kosice (8 slides) (Box 5)
  - Bonino gallery, 1967 (Box 5)
- Kosuth, Joseph, b. 1945 (7 slides) (Box 5)
  - Castelli gallery, 1971, 1972, 1975 (Box 5)
- Kotin (8 slides) (Box 5)
  - Byron gallery, 1964 (Box 5)
- Kozloff, Joyce, b. 1942 (4 slides) (Box 5)
  - de Nagy gallery, 1971, 1973 (Box 5)
- Kraft, Polly (6 slides) (Box 5)
  - Fischbach gallery, 1981, 1983, 1984 (Box 5)
- Kramer (6 slides) (Box 5)
  - Loeb gallery, 1965 (Box 5)
- Krashes (1 slide) (Box 5)
  - Amel gallery, 1965 (Box 5)
- Kreindler, Doris Barsky, 1901-1974 (9 slides) (Box 5)
  - Seligman gallery, 1967 (Box 5)
- Kricke, Norbert, 1922-1984 (4 slides) [Slide box 26] (Box 5)
  - Lefebre gallery, 1968 (Box 5)
- Kroeplin (3 slides) (Box 5)
  - Capricorn gallery, 1969 (Box 5)
- Krueger, Jack (2 slides) (Box 5)
  - Castelli gallery, 1968 (Box 5)
- Kruger, Louise, b. 1924 (2 slides) (Box 5)
  - Green Mt. gallery, 1973 (Box 5)
- Krugman, Irene, 1925-1982 (3 slides) (Box 5)
  - Spectrum gallery, 1968, 1969 (Box 5)
- Krupéncow (also Kupéncow) (3 slides) (Box 5)
  - Wickersham gallery, 1968, 1969 (Box 5)
- Krushenik (also Krushenek) (18 slides) (Box 5)
  - Pace gallery, 1967, 1968, 1969, 1970, 1972 (Box 5)
- Kuehn, Frances, b. 1943 (3 slides) (Box 5)
  - Hutchinson gallery, 1973 (Box 5)
- Kuehn, Gary, b. 1935 (7 slides) (Box 5)
  - Paula Cooper gallery, 1971 (Box 5)
- Kuhn, Walt (1 slide) (Box 5)
  - Sachs gallery, 1971 (Box 5)
- Kulicke, Robert M., b. 1924 (6 slides) (Box 5)
  - Kornblee gallery, 1969, 1972 (Box 5)
- Kurhajec, Joseph A., b. 1938 (3 slides) (Box 5)
  - Alan Stone gallery, 1965, 1969 (Box 5)
- Kurt, Kay, b. 1944 (6 slides) (Box 5)
  - Kornblee gallery, 1968, 1970 (Box 5)
- Kusama, Yayoi, b. 1929 (11 slides) (Box 5)
  - Castellane gallery, 1964, 1965, 1966 (Box 5)
- Kuwayama (2 slides) (Box 5)
  - Daniels gallery, 1965 (Box 5)
- La Hotan, Robert, L., b. 1927 (3 slides) (Box 5)
  - Kraushaar gallery, 1968 (Box 5)
- Laine, Lenore (7 slides) (Box 5)
  - East Hampton gallery, 1968 (Box 5)
- Laing, Gerald, b. 1936 (5 slides) (Box 5)
  - AFA, 1966 (Box 5)
  - Feigen gallery, 1966, 1967 (Box 5)
- Lam, Jeannette (8 slides) (Box 5)
  - Grand Central Moderns, 1966 (Box 5)
- Lamis, Leroy, b. 1925 (10 slides) (Box 5)
  - Jackson gallery, 1965 (Box 5)
  - Staempfli gallery, 1966, 1969 (Box 5)
- Landeberg, Linda (2 slides) (Box 5)
  - Sachs gallery, 1973 (Box 5)
- Landfield, Ronnie (4 slides) (Box 5)
  - Emmerich gallery, 1973, 1974 (Box 5)
- Lane, Christopher, b. 1937 (8 slides) (Box 5)
  - Findlay gallery, 1971 (Box 5)
- Lange, Achille (1 slide) (Box 5)
  - Hammer gallery, 1967 (Box 5)
- Langlais, Robert, 1921-1977 (9 slides) (Box 5)
  - Kornblee gallery, 1964 (Box 5)
  - Grippi gallery, 1964 (Box 5)
  - Iolas gallery, 1964 (Box 5)
  - Lee Ault gallery, 1971 (Box 5)
- Language III (Exhibition) (9 slides) (Box 5)
  - Various Artists (Box 5)
  - 1969 (Box 5)
- LaNowe, Terence (1 slide) (Box 5)
- Laskiewicz, Marie (2 slides) (Box 5)
  - Arras gallery, 1973 (Box 5)
- Leaf, June, b. 1929 (6 slides) (Box 5)
  - Frumkin gallery, 1968 (Box 5)
- Leeper, Doris (4 slides) (Box 5)
  - Schaeffer gallery, 1969, 1972 (Box 5)
- Lefebre (1 slide) (Box 5)
  - 1967 (Box 5)
- Leland (12 slides) (Box 5)
  - Sachs gallery, 1966 (Box 5)
- Lembeck, Jack, b. 1942 (2 slides) (Box 5)
  - Razor gallery, 1973 (Box 5)
- Lembeck, John (1 slide) (Box 5)
  - Spectrum gallery, 1972 (Box 5)
- Lenk, Douglas (9 slides) (Box 5)
  - Fischbach gallery, 1966, 1967 (Box 5)
- LeParc, Julio (18 slides) (Box 5)
  - Wise gallery, 1966, 1967, 1968 (Box 5)
  - Denise René gallery, 1973 (Box 5)
- Levi, Joseph (11 slides) [Slide box 27] (Box 5)
  - Wise gallery, 1965 (Box 5)
  - Stable gallery, 1966, 1967, 1969, 1970 (Box 5)
- Levine, Les, b. 1935 (9 slides) (Box 5)
  - Fischbach gallery, 1968, 1969, 1972 (Box 5)
- Levinson, Mon, b. 1926 (8 slides) (Box 5)
  - Kornblee gallery, 1968, 1971 (Box 5)
  - Weber gallery, 1973 (Box 5)
- Levy, Aaron (7 slides) (Box 5)
  - Phoenix gallery, 1966 (Box 5)
- Levy, Tibbie (2 slides) (Box 5)
  - Bodley gallery, 1968 (Box 5)
- Lewallen, Donald (2 slides) (Box 5)
  - O.K. Harris gallery, 1971 (Box 5)
- Lewis, Golda, d. 2005 (10 slides) (Box 5)
  - XX West gallery, 1966 (Box 5)
  - XX Cent West gallery, 1967 (Box 5)
- Lewitt, Sol, 1928-2007 (7 slides) (Box 5)
  - Dwan gallery, 1966, 1967, 1968, 1971, 1972 (Box 5)
- Liberman, Alex, 1912-1999 (1 slide) (Box 5)
  - "Continuous on Red," 1960 (Box 5)
- Lichtenstein, Roy, 1923-1997 (15 slides) (Box 5)
  - Castelli gallery, 1965, 1971 (Box 5)
  - AFA, 1966 (Box 5)
- Liebman (5 slides) (Box 5)
  - Stable gallery, 1968 (Box 5)
- Liebowitz (9 slides) (Box 5)
  - Westerly gallery, 1966 (Box 5)
  - Spectrum gallery, 1968 (Box 5)
- Lindner, Jean (3 slides) (Box 5)
  - Graham gallery, 1967 (Box 5)
- Lindner, Richard, 1901-1978b (11 slides) (Box 5)
  - Cordier-Ekstrom gallery, 1964, 1966, 1967, 1969 (Box 5)
- Lippold, Richard, 1915-2002 (11 slides) (Box 5)
  - Willard gallery, 1964, 1968 (Box 5)
- Lipsky, Pat, b. 1941 (5 slides) (Box 5)
  - Emmerich gallery, 1972, 1974 (Box 5)
- Lissitzky, El, 1890-1941 (1 slide) (Box 5)
  - Chalette gallery, 1964 (Box 5)
- Little, John (2 slides) (Box 5)
  - Sachs gallery, 1971 (Box 5)
- Lloyd, Elliot (3 slides) (Box 5)
  - Sachs gallery, 1971 (Box 5)
- Lloyd, Tom, b. 1929 (5 slides) (Box 5)
  - Amel gallery, 1965 (Box 5)
  - Wise gallery, 1968 (Box 5)
- Lobdell, Frank, b. 1921 (2 slides) (Box 5)
  - Jackson gallery, 1972 (Box 5)
- Lobe, Robert, b. 1945 (1 slide) (Box 5)
  - Bykert gallery, 1971 (Box 5)
- Lobel, Dan (1 slide) (Box 5)
  - Green Mt. gallery, 1973 (Box 5)
- Loew (4 slides) (Box 5)
  - Stable gallery, 1965 (Box 5)
- Londin, Barbara (4 slides) (Box 5)
  - Jason gallery, 1967 (Box 5)
- Loran, Erle, 1905-1999 (4 slides) (Box 5)
  - Schaefer gallery, 1965, 1967 (Box 5)
- Lorber, Stephen (2 slides) (Box 5)
  - Sachs gallery, 1973 (Box 5)
- Lorentzen, Ida (2 slides) (Box 5)
  - de Nagy gallery, 1982 (Box 5)
- Lorenzo (2 slides) (Box 5)
  - Kreisler gallery, 1969 (Box 5)
- Louis, Morris, 1912-1962 (28 slides) (Box 5)
  - Emmerich gallery, 1967, 1968, 1970 (Box 5)
  - L. Rubin gallery, 1969, 1971 (Box 5)
- Lorjou, Bernard, d. 1986 (1 slide) (Box 5)
  - E. Walter gallery, 1969 (Box 5)
- Love, Arlene (8 slides) (Box 5)
  - Dintenfass gallery, 1967 (Box 5)
  - Hutchinson gallery, 1972 (Box 5)
- Love, Jim, b. 1927 (2 slides) (Box 5)
  - Iolas gallery, 1964 (Box 5)
- Loving, Alan (3 slides) (Box 5)
  - Zierler gallery, 1971 (Box 5)
- Lozano, Lee, 1930-1999 (2 slides) [Slide box 28] (Box 5)
  - Bianchini gallery, 1966 (Box 5)
- Lucchesi (7 slides) (Box 5)
  - Forum gallery, 1966 (Box 5)
- Luken, Sven (9 slides) (Box 5)
  - Pace gallery, 1966, 1968, 1970 (Box 5)
- Lye, Len, 1901-1980 (3 slides) (Box 5)
  - Lye, Len, 1901-1980 (Box 5)
- Lynde, Clyde (3 slides) (Box 5)
  - Babcock gallery, 1969 (Box 5)
- Lynds (2 slides) (Box 5)
  - Babcock gallery, 1971 (Box 5)
- Lytle, Richard, b. 1935 (7 slides) (Box 5)
  - Borgenicht gallery, 1966 (Box 5)
- Maccio, Romulo, b. 1931 (5 slides) (Box 5)
  - Bonino gallery, 1965 (Box 5)
- MacEntyre, Eduardo, b. 1929 (5 slides) (Box 5)
  - Bonino gallery, 1968, 1970 (Box 5)
- Machlin (4 slides) (Box 5)
  - Waddell gallery, 1967 (Box 5)
- Machlin, Sheldon, 1918-1975 (4 slides) (Box 5)
  - Grippi-Waddell gallery, 1965 (Box 5)
- Mack, Heinz, b. 1931 (11 slides) (Box 5)
  - Wise gallery, 1964, 1966, 1968 (Box 5)
- MacWells (12 slides) (Box 5)
  - Sachs gallery, 1965, 1966, 1967 (Box 5)
- Magafan, Ethel, b. 1916 (3 slides) (Box 5)
  - Midtown gallery, 1969 (Box 5)